YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴： YY
后期： 瓜瓜  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： vero  非燕  一块二  猫中之王
后期： 瓜瓜  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期：瓜瓜 字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第九集
跟我来
Psst. In here!
-安全了  -未必
- I'm safe. - Not quite.
请把护身符交出来  斯丁森先生
The amulet, please, Mr. Stinson.
何必呢
Why?
-来人呀  救命呀  -孩子
- Help! Help! - The kid.
-救救我  -孩子  撑住
- Help! - Hang on, kid.
抓住我的领带
Grab my tie.
可你不该把领带摘下来
But you're not supposed to take the tie off.
你跟你的朋友莉莉和马修打赌输了
You lost a bet with your friends Lily and Marshall
所以你必须一整年都戴着这条领带
which requires you to wear the tie for a full year.
如果事关救人性命  我想他们会理解的
If it means saving your life, I think they'll understand!
光听他们的名字  就知道是好人
They sound like nice people!
没错
Yeah, they are.
他们可是大好人
They're very nice.
抓紧
Come on.
好了
That's it.
谢谢你  先生
Thanks, Mister.
我要怎么报答你的大恩大德呢
How can I repay you?
好好学习  天天向上
You can stay in school, that's how.
不要
No!
真人真事
True story.
天啊  我会超级想念那条小鸭领带滴
But golly, I'm just gonna miss the heck out of that ducky tie.
发自肺腑地想念
I really am.
瞧我在垃圾堆里发现了什么
Look what I just found in the trash.
不要
No!
孩子们  人的这辈子
Kids, you haven't truely lived,
严禁在旋转木马上吸烟
如果没被人当过反面教材  明令禁止
until somewhere, somebody puts a sign up.
那就真的是白活了
because of something you did
严禁拳击美洲驼]
赌场内严禁骑摩托
比如
For instance...
你们有没有看见外面的标牌上写着
Have you guys seen that sign out front that says
"绝对严禁在此趴板"
"Absolutely No Boogie-Boarding"?
那是怎么一回事
What's that all about?
那是个精彩的故事  你有时间听吗
Oh, that's a great story. You got time for it?
我该出发去我妈的生日派对了  所以...
Well, I'm supposed to go to my mom's birthday party, so...
你就尽可能地短话长说吧
please make it as long as you can.
故事发生在几个月前
Well, it happened a few months ago.
飓风来袭的那晚
The night of the hurricane...
孩子们  那是在2011年8月26日
Kids, it was August 26, 2011,
艾琳飓风直奔纽约而来
and Hurricane Irene was barreling towards New York.
各位  各位  各位
Guys, guys, guys.
这场风暴不容小觑
This storm is serious.
万幸的是  你们有朋友是童子军出身
Luckily, you are friends with a former Boy Scout.
童子军总是什么呢
And a Boy Scout is always what?
-无人爱  -被人打
- Unpopular? - Beaten up?
只能约老妈看电影
Going to the movies with his mom?
童子军总是做足准备
A Boy Scout is always prepared.
准备蹲在衣帽间里吃午饭
Prepared to spend lunch in his locker?
准备一辈子当处男
Prepared to die a virgin?
准备给姐姐涂指甲
Prepared to paint his sister's nails?
准备应对紧急情况
Prepared for emergencies!
所以一周前
That's why a week ago,
当艾琳还只是个热带低气压...
when Irene was just a tropical depression--
你就是个头脑发热的抑郁狂
You're a tropical depression.
这位童子军为我们准备了
This guy got us...
灾害应急包
a disaster backpack,
还租好一辆五人座的车  现在就停在外面
and a rental car that seats five, parked right outside.
我们要开车直奔我在韦斯切斯特的家
We're gonna drive up to my place in Westchester
到了那儿我们就安全了
where we'll all be safe.
童子军就是牛  不必客气
Boy Scouted! You're welcome.
泰德说得对  我们该去
Ted's right, we should go.
在出城的路上
Hey, on the way out of the city,
能顺便去我家拿点东西吗
do you mind if we stop at my place so I can get something?
好了  你要拿什么
Okay, what did you have to get?
我的小酒  我们哪儿也不去
My drink on. We're not going anywhere.
什么  不行
What? No!
没时间喝酒了  我们要立刻出发
We don't have time for this! We gotta get going!
-泰德  我比你年长  -没错
- Ted, I'm older than you. - Yeah.
-又比你高  -就年长而已
- And taller. - Just older.
等你长到我的岁数  我的高度
And when you reach my age, and height,
你就会发现飓风之类的事
you'll see that things like this hurricane
没什么大不了的
are no big deal.
桥就快封了
They're going to close the bridges.
各位  我们得赶紧离开这儿
You guys, we got to get out of here.
恐怕这次我同意金毛的观点
I'm afraid I'm with blondie on this one.
暴风雨不算什么  姐可是来自温哥华
This storm is nothing. I'm from Vancouver.
知道我们管这种天气叫什么吗
You know what we call this in the Couv?
烧烤的好天气
Barbecue weather.
就是  我同意他们的观点
Yeah, I'm with these guys.
坐在巴尼家的超屏电视前  喝着小酒
Drinking beer in front of Barney's giant TV
比坐在车里
beats sitting in the car
听着《艺妓回忆录》好多了
listening to Memoires of a Geisha.
拜托  我们都听到最精彩的部分了
Come on, we're at the best part.
是我妈  打来问我情况的
Oh, it's my mom, checking to see if I'm okay.
嗨  妈妈
Hey, Mom.
妈咪  外面下毛毛雨了
Ooh, Mommy! It's drizzling out!
我好怕怕哦
I'm so scared!
穿比基尼的好天气
Bikini weather.
马修  你同意我的观点  对吗
Marshall, you're with me, right?
抱歉  老朋友
Sorry, old friend.
可我冒不起这个险
But I can't afford to tempt fate.
对哦  当时的我有被害妄想症
Oh right, I was being really weird.
我要解释一下
I should explain.
去年夏天我辞去了工作
Last summer I quit my job.
就在飓风来临的一周前
And then, a week before the hurricane...
我的医疗保险过期了
Huh, my medical insurance just expired.
所以在加入你的医保计划前
That gives me two uninsured weeks
我有两周时间是无医保的
before I'm added to your plan.
没什么大不了的
It's no biggie.
被纸划了
Ow! Paper cut.
死亡无处不在
Death is all around us.
所以在接下来的两周
So for the next two weeks
他变成了个粘人的爱伦坡[惊悚推理小说家]
he was basically a really clingy Edgar Allan Poe.
死神在召唤
The Grim Reaper beckons.
我可以感觉到他用冰冷的手掐住我的喉咙
I feel his icy grip around my throat,
他的猎犬匍匐在我脚下喘着粗气
the breath of his hounds at my heels,
他的镰刀无休无止地敲打着我的房门
the unrelenting rat-tat-tat of his scythe on my chamber door.
而你  你随口提出的请求
And you, with your blithe request,
把我狠狠地推向了他的怀抱
you only hasten his inevitable triumph.
这就是你想要的吗
Is that what you desire?
这就是你想要的吗  莉莉
Is that what you desire, Lily?
我只是想要你去买点百吉饼
I just wanted you to get us some bagels.
百吉饼
Bagels?!
你有没有想过
Do you have any idea
我可能会在买百吉饼时遭遇不测
what could happen to me whilst getting bagels?!
怎么  不  我不要这样死
What the...?! No, not like this!
好吧  那我去买
Fine. I'll go get the bagels.
不行
No!
为什么不行
Why not?
记住  别加太多奶油干酪
And remember, not too much cream cheese.
最多加满半张饼
Half a shmear, max.
多谢  宝贝
Thanks, baby.
不不  我不要这样死
No! No! Not like this!
够了  你现在的想法也太扯了
Okay, now you're just being ridiculous.
人生本来就很扯  莉莉
Well, life is ridiculous, Lily!
人们会被公车碾
People get run over by buses
被滑板击中蛋蛋  被婴儿咬
and hit in the nuts by skateboards, bitten by babies.
没人一醒来就有预感
Nobody wakes up and says,
"今天我要在视频网站上出名"
"Today I'm gonna star in a YouTube video."
你已经说了不下十几遍了
You've said that at least a dozen times.
莉莉  接下来的两周
Lily, for the next two weeks
你必须寸步不离地保护我
you must be by my side protecting me.
至于吗  能出什么事
Why, what's gonna happen?
答案就是  飓风
Answer: a hurricane.
就让我把领带摘了吧  求你们了
Just let me take off the tie! Please!
我得戴着这条领带上班
I have to wear this at work.
你们能想象那有多糟糕吗
Do you have any idea what that's like?
如果证监会上诉  我们就全完蛋了
If the SEC pursues charges, it's going to be all our asses.
我比任何人还认真地对待这件事
Nobody takes this more seriously than I do.
求你了  我能摘了吗
Please, can I take it off?
你...可以...接
You... may... knot.
Knot发音同not  意为不能摘
着...戴
With a "K."
小小的领带双关语
A little tie pun.
这事没完
This is far from over.
你心中有个价码  埃里克森  我会找出来的
You have a price, Eriksen, and I will find it.
在今天结束前
When the end of day is nigh,
我一定会把领带摘下
I'll have taken off this tie.
我会喜欢我那时的样子  我保证
I'm going to like the way I look, I guarantee it.
-刚才说到趴板滑行...  -趴板滑行
- So boogie-boarding... - Boogie-boarding.
我想说服他们跟我走
So I was trying to get these guys to leave.
喂  阿呆
Hey, Nerdlinger,
瞧你那万事俱备的傻样
what's with the safety boner?
拜托
I mean, come on.
灾害应急包  汽车  女士雨靴
The disaster kit, the car, the ladies' rain boots--
是男士的
Uh, they're men's.
粉色是为了更容易被救援直升机发现
Pink is just easier to spot from the rescue chopper.
听着  原谅我为你们瞎操心了
Look, forgive me for caring about you guys,
可你们是我在这世上最好的朋友
but you're my best friends in the world
我只想确保你们都平安无事
and I just want to make sure you're okay.
泰德  你真是个大哭丧鬼
Ah. Ted, you are a giant whining bummer.
巴尼
Barney...
别杞人忧天了  泰德
Come on, Ted,
这场暴风雨没什么大不了的
this storm is not a big deal.
这场暴风雨很严重
This storm is a big deal.
让我们重播艾琳抵达北卡罗来纳州时
Let's replay that harrowing footage
那段令人痛心的画面吧
of Irene touching down in North Carolina.
我们得马上离开纽约
We gotta get out of here!
走  快点  快点
Go, go! Come on, come on!
-拜托就让我摘了吧  -不行
- Please let me take it off! - No.
-五千  -不行
- $5,000? - No.
他是认真的吗
Is he serious?
一万
$10,000?
-不行  -伙计们  点头吧
- No. - Dudes, take the money.
-两万  -不行
- $20,000? - No.
-行  -我让你扇我耳光
- Yes. - I'll let you slap me in the face
-下手多重都行  -这主意不错
- as hard as you can. - You have my attention.
孩子们  还记得马修和巴尼的耳光赌约吗
Kids, you remember Marshall and Barney's slap bet.
几年前  因为巴尼和马修打赌输了
A few years earlier, Barney lost a bet to Marshall.
他的惩罚是  随时随地可能会被扇耳光
His penalty was five slaps delivered anyplace, anytime.
迄今为止  马修扇了巴尼四个耳光
So far, Marshall had slapped Barney four times.
也就是说还剩最后一个
Which meant he only had one slap left.
你意下如何呀  马修
What do you say, Marshall?
你是要把握住这次"赏光机"
Are you going to seize this slap-ortunity
还是让这次机会从你指缝中流失
or let it slap through your fingers?
别让他得逞  马修
Don't let him tempt you, Marshall.
我不知道  莉莉  我们的宝宝快出生了
I don't know, Lily. I mean we have a baby on the way.
那个多余的耳光迟早能派上用场
An extra slap could really come in handy.
不  不行
No! No!
我怎么能动摇
This is crazy.
这条领带你必须再戴十个月
You having to wear that tie for another ten months
只有这样才能令我满意
is all the satisfaction I need.
再说了  我还有一个耳光没扇呢
Plus, I still have one slap left,
-感觉真好  -可如果你那个耳光也不剩了
- and that feels good. - But if you didn't have that slap left--
假设我今晚怂恿你扇了我
if say, I were to get you to slap me tonight--
我想到时可就大不相同了
I suppose that would change everything.
是的
I suppose it would.
游戏开始
Le jeu commence.
嘲笑马修不会说法语
我叫马修
Je m'appelle Marshall.
-刚才说到趴板滑行...  -趴板滑行
- So boogie-boarding... - Boogie-boarding.
我想说服他们跟我走
So I was trying to get these guys to leave,
不过有个小问题
but there was one little problem.
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go.
我不走
I'm staying.
怎么了  巴尼
What?! Barney?!
到时外面肯定会狂风乱作
Hey, hey, it's going to get pretty crazy out there.
如果哪个辣妹被吹得花枝乱颤衣服全没
And if some hot woman gets all her clothes blown off,
而我却没有录下来
and I'm not up here to videotape it
传到网上  那谁会代劳  联邦应急管理局吗
and put it up on the Internet, who will, FEMA?
拜托  睁大眼看重点
Come on, open your eyes.
不  不  你跟我们一起走
No, no, you are coming with us.
一个都不能少
We leave no man behind.
妈
Hey, Mom.
对  这双雨靴卖得可火啦
Uh, yeah, the boots were a big hit.
我得先去尿个尿
You know, I better pee.
可等我和莉莉回来的时候  我们都得走
But when Lily and I get back, we're all leaving.
等等  你尿尿我也要陪着吗
Wait, I have to go pee with you?
你想让我一个人去厕所吗
You want me to go to the "bathroom,"
那可是这房子里最危险的房间呀
the most dangerous room in the house by myself?
你有没有想过  我可能会遭遇不测
Do you have any idea what could happen?
我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
我看不见了
I'm blind!
不  不  我可不想这么死
No, no! Not like this!
我觉得对于这件事发生的可能性
I don't think we're seeing eye to eye
我们的看法不太相同
about the likelihood of that happening.
是我爸
Hey, it's my dad.
我爸打电话给我
My dad's calling me.
-你知道哪儿...  -泰德那雨靴是从哪儿买的吗
- Hey, do you know where...? - Ted got his boots?
-对  超好看  -搞得我也想买一双
- Yeah. They're fabulous. I totally want a pair.
好的  爸  我会的  谢谢
Okay, Dad, I will. Thanks.
伙计们  我爸说这场飓风比想象中严重
Guys, Dad says this hurricane is a bigger deal than you thought.
现在换我做主  我们要立刻撤退
I'm taking charge. We are getting out of here.
够了  每个人的父母都打电话来嘱咐
Okay, what is with everybody's parents calling
算是怎么回事
to check up on them?
不过是下了场小雨
It's just a little rain.
割草的好天气
Lawn-mowing weather.
室外地滚球的好天气
Bocce weather.
看来你爸不担心你  让你很郁闷呀
You're really bummed that your dad's not worried about you.
什么
What?!
我爸有什么好担心的
Eh... What would my dad be worried about?
担心我没涂够防晒霜吗
That I'm not wearing enough sunblock?
粉刷的好天气
House-painting weather.
泰德  你回来了
Ted, you're back.
我改变主意了  算我一个  快走吧
I've changed my mind. I'm in. Let's go.
是吗  我也改变主意了  不带你走
Yeah, I changed my mind, too. You can't come.
其他所有人  我们撤
Everybody else, we're moving out.
真够狠的
That's harsh.
知道还有什么够狠的吗  紫外线
You know what else is harsh? Ultraviolet light.
这周我在日光浴床上睡着了
I fell asleep in the tanning bed this week
我觉得我的脸颊都被晒伤了
and I think I got a sunburn on my cheek.
我的肤质太敏感了
It's so sensitive.
这半边脸就像一个红色的大靶心
It's like a big, red bull's-eye.
哎哟喂
Ouchie.
你是不是拿了我包里的腮红
Did you take my blush out of my purse?
话题回到趴板
So, boogie-boarding.
-回到趴板  -好  回到趴板
- So, boogie-boarding. - Boogie-boarding.
拜托  泰德
Oh, come on, Ted,
你不能就这样把他扔下
you can't just leave him here.
为什么不能
Uh, yeah, I can.
他说我是个大哭丧鬼
You called me a giant whining bummer.
你不准上我的车
You're not allowed in my car.
你也没法知道艺妓最后有没有找到真爱
You don't get to find out if the geisha finds love.
这是原则问题
This is about principle.
泰德  我准备好了
Hey, Ted. I'm ready to go.
肯定是你唤醒了他的"原则"吧
And you must be "Principle."
另外说一下  各位  这是玛雅
Ah, on a separate note, guys, this is Maya.
我刚在大厅遇到的
I just met her out in the hall.
我们有很多共同点
We have a lot in common,
比如我们都热爱乡村音乐
such as our mutual love of country music,
纳斯卡赛车  杰夫・兹沃西  不许插嘴
NASCAR and Jeff Foxworthy. Just go with it.
纳斯卡是美国国家赛车联合会的简称
杰夫・兹沃西是美国喜剧演员
她想搭个便车出城
She needed a ride out of the city,
我们又正好多个座位  所以
and we have an extra seat in the car, so...
好  我们出发吧
Okay, let's hit it!
事情居然演变成这样
Wow, it's come to this.
你本来可以帮助一个朋友
You could help a friend,
但你却选择了穿紧身吊带的辣妹
but instead, you're choosing the hot girl in the tight tank top.
你出师了
Your training is complete!
我真为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of this kid!
但话说回来  暴风就要来了
But seriously, the storm's coming in,
甩了这个小妞  咱们快撤吧
so dump the hoochie and wheels up.
但你说好捎上我的
You promised me a seat.
我的上帝啊
Oh, for God's sake.
你俩都去  我留下
You two both go. I'll stay here.
-什么  莉莉  别啊  -副驾归我
- What? Lily, no! - Shotgun!
-不带你  -那莉莉能去了
- You're staying. - Then Lily can come!
-什么  不不不  我就呆这儿  -为什么
- Wha...? No, no, no, I'll stay here. - Why?
因为我想一个人待会儿
I just want some time away from you!
什么
What?
马修  对不起  我爱你
Marshall, I'm sorry. I love you,
但我这个星期一点私人时间都没有
but I haven't had a second alone in weeks!
现在可是暑假呀
It's summer vacation!
我只想坐在浴缸里
All I want to do is sit in the bathtub
静静地看书  但现在
and read a book, but now...
宝贝  我忘了拿书进来
Baby, I forgot to bring a book.
你不介意大声念给我听吧
Do you mind reading yours out loud?
我也没觉得有多好啊
Hey, it's been no picnic for me either.
你的声音都没有分角色
You don't even do the voices.
匿名电话
Blocked number.
你好
Hello?
RJ吗  我是爸爸
RJ? It's your father.
爸爸
Daddy?
我爱你
I love you.
你的电话对我来说意义重大
It means so much that you called.
我就知道你在等你爸电话
Ha! I knew that you wanted him to call.
被我猜对了吧
Busted!
刚才是你
That was you?
我真觉得你该扇他
I really think you should slap him.
绝对该扇
You should slap him!
-使劲扇  -使劲扇
- Slap him. - Slap him.
两边脸  出手吧
Two cheeks, no waiting.
很好  因为我真的忍不住了
Good, 'cause I really think I'm gonna slap him!
-话说趴板  -继续趴板
- So, boogie-boarding? - Boogie-boarding.
拜托  泰德
Come on, Ted.
你宁可载不认识的妓女
You're gonna give some random floozy a ride,
也不愿意载巴尼
but not take Barney?
妓女
Floozy?!
如果有她  我就不去了
If she's going, I'm not going!
莉莉  你留这儿  我们走
Lily, you're staying. Let's go.
如果莉莉不去  我也不去
If Lily's staying, then I'm staying!
-那我走  -那我也走
- Then I'm going. - Then I'm going.
你留下  马修  因为我要去
You can't go, Marshall, 'cause I'm going.
-如果巴尼去  我就不去  -那我就能去了
- If Barney's going, I'm not going! - Then I can go.
-那我不去了  -我也不去了
- Then I'm staying. - Then I'm staying.
-那我去  -那我就不去了
- Then I'm going. - Then I'm not going.
你们爱去不去  反正我是要走
Okay, you know what? I'm going.
多普勒雷达连续一周都在报这场暴风雨
This storm's been on Doppler radar for a week.
我是唯一一个为之做准备的人
I'm the only one who prepared for it.
你们还都嘲笑我  所以我决定
And you all made fun of me. So guess what?
童子军要孤身上路了  再见
This Boy Scout is taking a hike. Good-bye!
玛雅  问一句
Maya, real quick,
你觉得咱俩有戏吗
did you think there was anything here, or...
我有男朋友
Oh, I have a boyfriend.
再见
Good-bye!
泰德
Um, Ted...?
疏散时间已经结束
The time for evacuation is over.
在天气情况好转前
Everyone should now go inside and be prepared
大家请留在室内
to stay inside until weather conditions improve,
在周日下午前  请勿外出
which won't likely be until Sunday afternoon.
我们被困住了吗
We're stuck here?
大伙儿别慌
Okay, let's not panic.
你们可以慌了
You know what? Let's panic.
如果我们熬不过今晚
Hey, if we don't make it through the night,
我希望你们知道  我是发自肺腑地后悔
I want you guys to know, and I really mean this...
20多岁时没拓展交际圈  多交几个朋友
I wish I had branched out and made more friends in my 20s.
好了  我要去厕所了
Well, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
只身前往
By myself, I guess.
小心有熊出没哦
Watch out for bears.
既然我们都快完蛋了
Since this might be the end,
那我就坦白一件事吧
I gotta confess something.
可以吗
Can I?
如你所愿
Might as well.
其实  我跟巴尼有一腿
Barney and I have been doing the wild thing...
一直在暗中偷情
this whole time.
去年短暂地停过一阵
Except a brief period last year
因为当时他忙着搞马修的妈妈
when he was shacking up with Marshall's mom.
但幸运的是  当时我们有一起玩3P  所以
but luckily, three-ways were on the menu, so...
马修  你知道她根本没说这些  对吧
Marshall, you know she didn't say any of that, right?
我知道  可我就是想狠狠地扇他
I know, but I just want to slap him so bad!
但那条领带看着又那么弱智
But that tie is so stupid!
但那巴掌扇起来又那么爽
But the slap would feel so good!
但他又那么讨厌那条领带
But he hates that tie so much!
也许我能帮你
Perhaps I can help.
马修  你好好想一想
Marshall, ask yourself this question:
为什么是今天
why today?
他在过去的几个星期  都毫无怨言
He hasn't said anything about that tie for weeks,
可突然就在今天
and yet, suddenly today,
他怎么连一秒都忍不住了
he can't wear it another second?
凡事皆有因
No, there's a reason.
你接下来一定有什么重要的事
You've got something coming up.
因为它  你就象待宰的羔羊
Something where you're on display,
无力反抗
vulnerable...
被迫示众
exposed.
这和工作无关
It's not work-related.
对  应该是和感情有关
No, this is relationship stuff.
你想给某人留下好印象
You're trying to impress someone.
在你一开始编的故事里
In the lie you told,
你说有两个暴徒在追杀你
you said you were being chased by two goons.
所以你要见的是两个人
So it's two people.
或许是一对夫妇
A couple, perhaps.
你明天要去见诺拉的父母
You're meeting Nora's parents tomorrow!
猜错了
Wrong!
错上加错  大错特错
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
其实是后天  人家真的很想讨得他们的欢心
It's in two days, and I really want them to like me!
专家就是牛
Oh-ho! Therapisted!
你是心理医生  还是精神病医生
Shrinked? Shrunk?
我们回头再研究吧
We'll figure it out.
那么  说回滑板的事
So, boogie-boarding.
继续趴板的故事
Boogie-boarding.
莉莉  能和你单独说点事吗
Hey, Lily, can I talk to you for just a second?
马修  如果你叫我进来是帮你刷牙的话
Marshall, if I'm in here to brush your teeth,
老娘誓将
I swear to...
抱歉  我这段时间这么黏人
I'm sorry that I've been so needy lately.
我明白你需要时间独处
I know that you need some time alone.
我去其他房间呆着
So... I'll be in the other room.
你哪儿也别想去
You're not going anywhere.
妙就妙在  那晚过后
And the funny thing is, after that night,
我们从此不再孤单
we'll never be alone again.
你们居然在我的浴室播种
You made that in my bathroom?
无心插柳柳成荫
Whoops.
哇  飓风送子
Wow, a hurricane baby.
天啊  小旋风・埃里克森是个好名字
Oh, man, Hurricane Eriksen would be a sweet name.
是个相当好的名字
It would be a crazy sweet name!
我谢谢你全家  泰德
Thanks, Ted.
不管怎样  第二天  警报解除后
Anyway, the next day, after the danger had passed...
酒吧不开门
It's closed.
现在我们干嘛
Now what?
童子军总是做足准备
A Boy Scout is always prepared.
真棒
Nice!
为平安度过飓风而干杯
To surviving the hurricane.
-我爱你们大家  -我们也爱你
- I love you guys. - Love you.
我终于在几天后  如愿去一趟韦斯切斯特的家
I did finally make it up here to the house later that week
却发现客厅里躺着
only to find that a falling oak tree had
一棵连根拔起的橡树
landed in the living room.
如果当时我们在那里
If we'd been here,
一定会被大树砸得稀巴烂
it would have crushed us like bugs.
所以孩子们  你永远没法确定
You see, kids, there's no way of knowing for sure
什么地方最安全
where the safest place is...
所以你只能期望  能有三两好友陪在身旁
so the best you can hope for is to have some good company.
各位  你们说我用这个趴板能滑出多远
Guys, how far do you think I can boogie-board on this thing?
心有多远  就滑多远
So far!
马修  新的医疗保险明天才开始啊
Marshall, your insurance doesn't kick in till tomorrow.
你们知道吗
Yeah, well, you know what?
人要活在当下
Life kicks in right now.
别担心  他第一次
Don't worry, he wasn't hurt...
伤得不重  我有急救夹板
the first time. I have splints!
不过第二次  他直接穿破了麦凯伦的前窗
The second time he went through the front window of Maclaren's.
这就是"不准在此趴板"标牌的由来
Hence the "No Boogie-boarding" sign.
好了  各位  我得走了
All right, guys, I gotta go.
巴尼  祝你拜见岳父母顺利
Barney, good luck with Nora's parents.
-拜拜  -拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
回见
See you later.
See you.
巴尼
Hey, Barney?
我们在你家浴室
Listen, um, we made a baby
造人成功
in your bathroom.
所以我们欠你一份情
So we owe you one.
我们决定
So we say...
你可以取下你的小鸭领带了
you can take off the ducky tie.
代价是  三个耳光
For three slaps.
三个耳光吗
Three slaps?
先说好  是在马修还剩一耳光的基础上
And to be clear, this would add three slaps
再加三耳光
to Marshall's existing one,
所以总计是  四个耳光
giving him four slaps in total.
成交
Deal.
我解放了
I'm free!
天啊  感觉如此美好
God, this feels so good!
我觉得我错了
This was a mistake!
我还是乖乖戴着领带吧
I wanna put the tie back on!
快把领带还给我
我干嘛选在这时候恢复本色呢
Why do I have to be Barney right now?
还有三个耳光
Three slaps remaining!
还有三个  我真喜欢那清脆的声音
Three slaps. Wow, I like the sound of that.
我要把剩下这三个耳光攒着
I think I'll save those bad boys,
以备不爽之需
you know, for a rainy day.
很好  苦难已经结束了
Okay. The worst is over.
还剩两个耳光
Two slaps remaining!
没事了
It's all right.
都结束了
Hey, it's all done...
下次接着扇
for now.
我觉得我要回家
I think I need to go home
重新审视我的决策能力
and reevaluate how I make life decisions.
来吧  我也要回去工作了
Come on. I have to go back to work.
-我们一起搭计程车吧  -好的
- Let's split a cab. - Okay.
你和他们说过
Did you ever tell those guys
另外那件差点发生的事吗
about that other thing that almost happened?
另外的那件事
That other thing?
你说那件事啊  我没说  你呢
Oh, that. No. Did you?
我也没说
No.
我很抱歉打了那个电话
Hey, I'm really sorry about that phone call.
没关系
Oh, it's fine.
不  怎么会没关系呢  我真是混蛋
No, it is so not fine. I was a jerk.
如果你不介意的话  我想说
And if you don't mind my saying,
你爸居然不打给你  他就是个彻头彻尾的蠢蛋
your dad is a complete idiot for not calling.
他应该每天都打电话给你
He should never let a day go by without calling you
因为我要是一整天没和你说上话
because when I let a day go by without talking to you...
那一天  都黯淡无光
Um, that day's just no good.
抱歉
Um, sorry.
是我爸
It's my dad.
等一下  把手拿出来
Wait, show me your hands.
绝对不是我
My hands.
你好啊老爸
Hey, Dad!
我就说嘛
That's what I've been saying!
高尔夫球天
Golf weather!
你能相信我们差点就
Can you believe we almost...?
我知道
I know.
幸好我们没做下去
Good thing we didn't.
在那不久以后
Yeah. I mean, not long after that
你就和诺拉在一起了
you got together with Nora.
你也遇到了凯文
And you met Kevin.
我们也算"死里逃生"
Yeah. Disaster averted.
没错
Exactly.
要是我们真的做了  一切就毁
It would've ruined everything if we'd been all...
喇  喇  喇  喇  喇
ah-la-la-la...
对啊  太傻了
I know, right? So dumb...
喇  喇  喇  喇  喇
ah-la-la-la...
喇舌[终于>_<]
La-la-la-la...